In the example in the quiz, the math says the result should be 1.0.
在测试题的例子中 数学运算的结果应为 1.0
But, the code says 0.95.
但代码运行的结果为 0.95
That's a big difference.
这是很大的差异
Go ahead, replace the one billion with just one, and
你可以试一下 将 1000000000 替换为 1
you'll see that the error becomes very tiny.
会看到误差会变得非常微小
We're going to want the values involved in the calculation of this
我们希望 我们所关心的这一巨大的损失函数所涉及的值
big lost function that we care about, to never get too big or too small.
不要太大 也不要太小
One good guiding principle is that we always want our variables to have 0 mean
一个较好的指导原则就是 使变量尽可能保持
and equal variance whenever possible.
0 均值  和相同的方差
On top of the numerical issues, there are also a really good
除了有利于值运算之外 在做优化时
mathematical reasons to keep values you compute roughly around a mean of zero
保持 0 均值 和相同的方差
and equal variance when you're doing optimization.
也有很好的数学理由
A badly conditioned problem means that the optimizer has to do
如果问题设计得不好 优化器需要做大量的搜索
a lot of searching to go and find a good solution.
来找到好的解决方案
A well conditioned problem makes it a lot easier for
如果问题设计得好 那么优化器的工作
the optimizer to do its job.
会轻松许多
If you're dealing with images it's simple.
如果你处理的是图像 就简单了
You can take the pixel values of your image, they are usually between 0 and
你可以将图像的像素值 通常在 0 到 255
255.
之间
And simply subtract 128 and divide by 128.
减去 128 再除以 128
It doesn't change the content of your image, but it makes it much easier for
它不会改变图像的内容
the optimization to proceed numerically.
但从数学角度而言 优化会更容易进行
You also want your weights and biases to be initialized at
你还希望 权重和偏差
a good enough starting point for the gradient descent to proceed.
有一个理想的初始化值 有利于做梯度下降
There are lots of fancy schemes to find good initialization values.
找到好的初始化值的方法琳琅满目
But we're going to focus on a simple general method.
但我们会重点来看一个简单的通用方法
Draw the weights randomly from a Gaussian distribution would mean zero and
从高斯分布上随机获取初始权重
standard deviation sigma.
使这些权重的均值为 0 标准差为 σ
The sigma value determines the order of magnitude of your outputs
σ 值决定了在初始化时
at the initial point of your optimization.
你的输出的数量级
Because of the softmax on top of it, the order of magnitude also determines
因为上面还加了 Softmax 函数 其数量级也决定了
the peakiness of your initial probability distribution.
你的初始概率分布的陡峭程度
A large sigma will mean that your distribution will have large peaks,
σ 较大 则说明你的分布会集中在峰值处
it's going to be very opinionated.
表示确定性很强
A small sigma means that your distribution is very uncertain about
σ 较小 则表示你的分布
things.
确定性很弱
It's usually better to begin with an uncertain distribution, and
通常 从确定性弱的分布开始比较好
let the optimization become more confident as the training progress.
然后通过训练 让优化器的确定性越来越强
So, use a small sigma to begin with.
所以 初始时取小的 σ
Okay, so
好
now we actually have everything we need to actually train this classifier.
我们现在万事俱备 可以训练分类器了
We've got our training data, which is normalized to have zero mean and
我们有了训练数据 已经归一化好了 具有 0 均值
unit variance.
和单位方差
We multiply it by a large matrix, which is initialized with random weights.
我们将它乘以一个大的矩阵 即权重随机初始化矩阵
We apply the softmax then the cross-entropy loss and
应用 softmax 函数和交叉熵误差函数
we calculate the average of this loss over the entire training data.
然后计算此误差在整个训练集上的平均值
Then our magical optimization package computes
然后用我们神奇的优化工具
the derivative of this loss with respect to the weights in to the biases, and
对误差函数求权重和偏差的偏导
takes a step back in the direction opposite to that derivative.
根据导数值反向调整一步
And then, we start all over again,
再重做一遍
we repeat the process until we reach minimum of the loss function.
重复此过程 直到获得误差函数的最小值